I give you a gift.
YEARS BEFORE ...
Almost ready!
Any day, you will
to kill us from pneumonia.
Oh, do not be exaggerated!
Do you know that ink has to
be rinsed with cold water.
We, the Rosa Valdivia,
we had the luck
of being born in D.F.,
but good luck
to look like gringos.
Seriously, you think
we look like gringos
with that fake tincture?
How do you want
that I begin?
Once upon a time there were two sheep
married mesti as
and had a little lamb
that was born black
like the bitch who gave birth to him! "
Your turn, bitchy girl.
Ave Maria Pur ssima,
I confess to being me
everywhere.
that is,
of wanting to be another.
Oh, Carmen,
thank you.
The Red Cross should
give you a place of honor
for all your donations.
Who should you be?
received with honor to the mr.
You're making a
awesome work
with the helpless.
We, the ones we have the most,
we are the ones who should give the most.
When's the next dinner?
Ah, in a fortnight.
But do not worry,
I'll let you know.
Good evening, Carmen.
Violet,
nothing to tell them
stories of fear
before bedtime.
- Did you hear me?
- Yes.
And they know why you
They have to be erased early.
the bedroom lights?
So that no
withdraw the subsidy.
That's right, genius!
Violetta, anything,
call us
Goodnight My Loves.
Because
Do you call her Violetta?
I always wanted to
her name is Violetta.
Your family
it was the one who insisted
in calling it Rosalba.
Listen, you know.
what animal is washed
with hosepipes
cold water
Pigs.
And we are not
pigs for bathing
with cold water, or are we?
Who wants to play
Beauty salon?
We buy
mattresses, refrigerators ...
Dear...
...come here.
- Stupid! Stupid!
- There! There!
- You naughty girl!
- Give it!
Give me more in you what you
do with this family
with your crazy plans!
- Crazy and dumb girl!
- What's going on?
Your daughter does not know
What to be ashamed of?
Nor will you ever know!
What did she do now?
Yesterday, I bathed in
brothers with hot water.
And it was not just that, I ended up with
your imported conditioner.
Open!
I can not stand her anymore!
I do not mind her!
What did these
nuns taught you?
You will see
how do you change your attitude
when to start school
for secretaries.
No, no, no.
I refuse to pay
the studies of this year,
ungrateful
And what if she
end up being assistant
from the president
of a multinational!
"Maybe I'll get you a husband."
- Yes, very good.
The only way
it is useful.
of becoming
Something useful, said the "deer."
The only way
I was going to New York.
In my head,
New York, it was the opposite
to be in my house
as it springs.
Since I was a kid, I had
obsession for New York.
I cut and paste photos
in my wardrobe.
I imagined walking the streets
with my hair nig rrimo.
And laughed at the thought
in my father
Selling me a hot dog
and stealing my change.
YEARS BEFORE ...
I brought you a sandwich.
Make a space for me.
Mommy, how old?
Do you think I have it?
What's up? How many you have!
For me, you always
will be my spoiled boy.
Oh, I do not understand
What you do so much here.
So much time stuck
on this computer.
I told you, I have a blog.
Well. Eat it,
because otherwise, it cools.
This is  torradinho ,
as we like.
Young lady
...wake up!
Do you know what day today?
The worst day of my life?
Late afternoon.
And I have to go to the bank today.
to deposit the donations
of the Red Cross.
Do you want to get fired?
Come on, get up!
- There!
- ... and dress!
Are you going to do anything today?
Good morning ladies.
And who's this?
I do not know, but the dye
it was not enough
for these eyebrows
of taturana.
Today we have
a new companion.
Rosalba,
Do you want to introduce yourself?
Hi everybody,
I'm 18,
and I'm here
because my dream
become a secretary.
My name is Rosalba, but I prefer
Call me Violetta.
Violetta is the name
world.
No,
Rosalba is even more kitschy.
Even.
How was it?
"Shit," this school.
This little mouth.
Wash dishes.
Good afternoon Miss,
How are you?
- Normal.
- How nice.
Here's what I owed you.
from last week.
- Thank you very much.
- And that's the plant ...
Mom, I'm going
pick up the tea towel.
It's fine. And when
you finish the kitchen,
Carry on with
the dining room, you?
And what's yours? Since when
can you peek out the window?
I swear that it was
the first time.
Yeah, you seemed
an expert.
I swear.
There it is.
I do not care
May you see me.
I'll propose a deal.
I want you to steal from
his father the 500 pesos
that my mother is done
to give it to him.
If my father finds out
that I am
Taking money, it kills me.
Why do this?
without him discovering you.
Do you like to see me?
Would you like to see more?
A lot more?
With one condition.
I do not want 500 pesos ...
I want the same note
that my mother
gave to his father.
In fact, I made a
"V" in the corner.
If it is not the same note,
has no agreement.
And if there is no agreement,
I'll see myself at the
shameful need
to tell my mother
That you're a pig.
The assassination of Archduke
Francisco Fernando,
heir to
Austro-Hungarian crown,
and his wife,
the archduchess Sofia,
triggered hostilities.
Very important
let the names know
two countries
who participated
on the fronts.
I think what
you are writing,
Much more important
than anything
that I can say
about
the First World War.
Why not?
share with everyone?
No, thank you.
Sorry, but it was not
a proposal.
Start with the title.
We will not continue
while you speak
"Reasons I'm better
than the rest of the world. "
"Reason one.
"At the end, I feel that time
swallows me slowly
"inside
of his bowels. "
Wow, now the pig
became a poet!
Silence!
Continues.
"I open a door,
"and there are my parents.
"The two dead
after the accident
"And at the same time, alive,
surprised
for my visit.
"I tell them that
I'm passing through.
"That in five minutes
I have to go
"back to reality ...
"... but that I am the only person
"that can travel in time
"every time I feel like it.
"End of reason one."
I think the hamburger
yesterday made me sick.
That's weird.
You did not hurt anyone else!
You're not hot.
I can not go to school.
What do you want? That I
vomit in front of everyone?
What a joke!
It's fine. Stay.
I'm going to the aerobics.
When you feel
a little better,
fold the clothes
that I left in bed.
Now yes,
gardener baby son of the m e.
You'll see just what's good!
That day was the
my great debut
And you know what I discovered?
To be desired
It's a heavy drug.
You plate
Which school
for secretaries!
Music taught me
to speak English
I would like to score
a time with ...
Mr Waltz.
I would like to score
a time with Mr. Waltz.
Rosalba ...
... can you tell us what the
your plans for summer?
Discolor the "pussy".
You know what I
I will do this summer?
I'm going to be a millionaire.
By the way, my name is Violetta.
Very well.
I saw you, Pig!
If you go and make gossip,
I swear I'll kill you.
Calm  vei ,
I'm by your side.
And what do you want in return?
Nothing, I'm sorry, I'm yours.
side, I already told you.
That day, man,
I did not know
about your parents
and all that
I liked very much
of what you read, you know?
Yeah, I do not.
Take it, you did not see anything.
Old man, if you do not like it
of what he writes,
open a blog
more funny or something.
Let's see if he's okay.
I'll go right away
call a physician.
- Hey, give it to me, my!
- Yes, Mr. Carraldi.
I have deposited the 50,000 pesos.
In a little while I'll tell you
or proof.
- Give it to me, give me! Oh my!
- Good afternoon to you.
Let's see, be quiet!
- Oh, Mommy! Mommy!
- There!
Oh my God! Carmem!
You just bit him, man.
And now, yes,
we arrived at the beginning
of true history.
It turns out that everyone
the weights my mother
collected at dinner
of the Red Cross,
the mother daughter's thief
deposited
a part in the bank,
and the other, she changed
for dollars for her.
Here, pay attention,
Devil, why did he start?
the history of how
I became a rich girl,
and I started to be ... me.
Knowing
What did my mother do?
a little tart bills
for the Red Cross,
it seemed very convenient
promote the gardener,
with a robbery
that it was worth more.
Do not run.
You know when suddenly
you jump a wall
and even knowing that it is
very high, you think:
"No one I know of
It jumped so high. "
Let's see, can you stay calm?
I brought you here
because I have
a mission for you.
I can not do
Nothing with my arm.
This you go
to be able to do, yes.
Throw something
from my mother's purse.
But you take it when I
I ask you, okay?
What happened
with our agreement, eh?
I just do
extra work.
Well, the devil
with the agreement.
I torro yours.
quick money
It's no good to me.
There's no way. If your mother
catch me, she kill me.
You want everybody
know it
How did you break your arm?
Good.
I promise you it will be easy.
The little gardener
was my first accomplice.
But do not be shy.
Or, stay, if you want.
I did not count
with divine intervention
who filled with guilt or idiot.
The church bells?
The church bells!
God do not give you so much fear
when you get me
spying, and that yes,
that   mortal sin.
Forgive me.
I do not forgive you.
Give me the keys.
Give me
Your mother had a lot of
money in the purse?
What's up? Smelly!
I do not understand
Why do you want so much money?
There's your house, there's your school.
You do not lack anything.
I do not need anything
I need to be the
that I want to be.
You ... because you're one
slave who likes to own.
I ... I am my own mistress.
What? Do you really think?
that I conform
to go to school
of coarse secretaries?
Or being like my parents,
half-bowl thieves
Who are the charity?
I'm full of being a maid,
of not having a penny,
of not being able to take a shower
with a water
at least lukewarm.
What? Do you really think?
that I own
I can not give myself a life
less frightening?
Oh, get out!
Come on, get out! No
I want to see you again!
What the hell is that, Rosalba?
Dad, I do not want to go back.
to see this guy.
He was spying on me.
through the window.
"How dare you!"
- In my own house!
"Why did you do that?"
- You were spying!
- Damn it!
Violet?
- Violet?
- Yes, Mom.
Your father has already told me
which the shameless did.
I do not want to talk
about it, Mom.
Do not think I'm stupid.
Men only look
when they have something to look at.
Set the table.
Your brothers are hungry.
A , for a!
Here.
What's up?
Where did you get that?
A friend lent me.
They lent you this?
Was.
Yeah, idiot of
who lent you.
And idiot is still
you return.
Tell them they stole you.
What a good idea!
There! And now,
What happened to you?
Excuse me.
Can I get the broom?
To their disgrace,
me and them,
we had to
same logic.
And for my luck,
their security system
was very friendly.
I set everything up
so that no one noticed
the change of residence
of the money.
And I went down to clean, like
if nothing had happened.
Now that she was a rich girl,
I used to tend
how they were fucked!
I saw them and said:
What the fuck are they laughing at?
Because I had already left
they are very poor.
The tragedy
of "motherfuckers",
That your children do well
more "motherfuckers" than them.
You're going to say I do not do it.
But I do not care now.
What do you think?
Imagine me happy,
surrounded by notes,
and point.
Tell me the truth,
Did you start the fire?
- It was not me.
- You swear?
Okay, it was me, yeah.
What's up?
You heard the director.
They have no evidence.
Therefore they can not
do anything with me
They are lost,
because they are losers.
But because you
Do these things?
He forced me to read my blog
in front of the whole room.
He teased.
"What did you read?"
- Nothing, you would not understand.
- Why?
- Because you do not understand.
Because she's old.
Ah, you're ashamed to
May your mother be an old woman?
You're not my mother.
My mother is dead.
Shame on me for being a son.
of a dead woman.
Open that door!
We already know what you did.
We have to talk.
What did you do?
What did you do with
Your beautiful blond hair?
First, it takes bombs
in school and now this!
Let's see, you are like this.
Why did I pump?
And you think little?
You're not going to walk like this.
with that hair of a prostitute.
You're our calvary.
What we did for
deserve such a daughter?
You are pretentious,
"wannabes" shit!
- Rosalba!
My name is Violetta!
- You do not have a drug!
- Go to boarding school!
Rosalba!
Open that door!
Where are you going?
- Where do you think you're going?
- You cocks!
What an idiot!
That's what makes me angry and
to leave like this, without further ado.
Now I had to go back
l  to get my money.
Because it was
My money, you know?
Shit! Shit!
Shit!
Oh, Devil ...
It's better when you write this,
do not put me in the car
so alone and crying.
Make up something better.
No it's allowed
park here,  loirinha .
I'm going.
Loirinha   whore who
Brought you, horned!
Mom ...
...I'm so sorry.
OK.
We accept your
Sorry, little girl.
But it's not that easy.
You already know what
Your father and I thought.
If you think the
It's better than I see
for boarding school, that's fine.
It's going to have to be this way!
Dad...
Can we stop at the church?
That I want
confess with the priest.
- Ave Maria Pur ssima.
- Sin conceived.
Speak, child.
I do not even know where
begin, father.
For what most afflicts you, daughter.
Good...
I stole thousands
of my parents' dollars.
Thousands of dollars, daughter?
Two hundred seventeen thousand.
They were
stored in the closet.
Of all charges
charity dinners
of the Red Cross.
I think love
for the money of others
Come to me from family.
Do you believe in this
history of 100 years
of forgiveness for those who
steals a thief?
It's true
What are you telling me, daughter?
This money can not be
in the hands of sinners.
If you want God to forgive you,
You have to hand over the money.
the poor.
Which of them, Father?
Bring the money here to
the church and we will share it.
Of course, son of a bitch!
I come tomorrow
make you rich.
Allow me
Five minutes, please?
Sure, Father.
I told you that I thought
tell you the whole truth.
But, as you would say:
"Who am I,
to know who I am? "