Sometimes I feel
you won’t believe a thing.
But the truth is,
I was very nervous.
I crossed the border
like any other poor devil.
I’m American.
Remember it was
Violetta who crossed,
not Rosalba.
Violetta was bold
and willing
to have it her way.
Do you get it?
You always get me, Pig.
Come on, motherfuckers!
Get down!
Hurry up, assholes,
you’re now on the right side!
What’s in that suitcase?
Clothes.
You should really love
your clothes...
to show that much skin.
I can show you if you want.
All right!
BASED ON
XAVIER VELASCO'S NOVEL
CHAPTER 2
FASTER THAN SUPERMAN
My parents won’t know.
You speak Spanish.
I’m Eric.
Okay, I’ll stay at your place,
but just for tonight.
I’m Violetta.
And I did run away from home.
If Eric hadn’t shown up,
I would have been deported
the next day.
I was on the right side
of the border,
but far away from New York.
I needed Eric.
Take note,
”Diablo Guardián”,
here starts the chapter:
"Superman rescues Violetta".
- What’s up, 'Caiman'!
- I’m glad you came, dude!
How are you? Come in.
Want a cigarette?
Good for you.
Tobacco kills.
- Where’s “Caimana”?
- Over there.
Let’s go.
She’s loaded today.
That way.
Be right back.
This way.
What’s up, Caimana!
How are you, Pig?
I’ve got your order.
Three squares.
They’re really good.
If you take another two,
it’ll be 40 dollars.
They’re top quality.
All right!
Do you want fresh cannabis?
It just arrived.
- It’s top-notch.
- The best in the area.
No, thanks.
So, you don’t want
to go to New York?
But, do you want to be an actor?
Well, you don’t know yet.
You haven’t tried.
Sit down! Come!
Why don’t you come with me?
Well, but dreams come true.
What’s your dream?
To be rich.
- What are you doing?
- Imagine you’re in New York!
What would make you
the happiest man?
Perfect!
We’ll fly to Broadway tomorrow!
Are you crazy?
But I do.
Who cares...
For any other woman,
the first kiss tastes
like lust, romance,
like "I’m the happiest girl!"
For me, it was like
a stamp on the passport.
Could you describe
the exact turns
of a roller coaster?
No, me neither.
But before I knew, Superman
had taken me flying to New York.
Isn’t it the most wonderful place
you’ve ever seen?
You won’t think I’ll get
to the Royal Vanderbilt
looking like a hobo.
You should also change clothes
for your auditions.
Nothing, I’m just saying,
"dress for success".
And I want to be very successful.
My dad’s an asshole
that doesn’t even know where I am!
But does your mother know?
No, she believes I’m in Houston.
Expensive clothes
are like... I don’t know, a magnet.
Something that you want
and that makes you feel wanted.
- You’re crazy!
- No, I’m just happy.
Hey! Can we talk
in English all the time?
I want people to think I’m American.
Thanks for the sweet words.
- Sweet words?
- Yeah!
Money tickled me.
Hey! To the men’s department!
Eric was so nice,
he didn’t make any questions.
If Eric taught me
to make love,
I could teach him
tons of stuff
that are only possible
when you have
thousands of dollars.
I have 200 thousand dollars
in the suitcase.
For now,
one thing was certain...
I wouldn’t let Eric
deny me anything.
What’s up, dude!
You opened another blog, right?
You listened to me.
I’ve read it, it’s cool.
You’ve got attitude.
Wanna read what I’m working on?
Yeah, show me.
It’s cool, dude.
What a shitty country, man.
Hey! They call you "Sapo", right?
You know they do, dude.
What are you doing later, Sapo?
Nothing. The usual.
I mean, I’ll watch a movie.
Would you go with me on a trip?
Where to?
Come in.
Damn it, dude! This screen is huge!
- You can grab the girls' boobs...
- Don’t touch the screen, man.
- You’ll stain it.
- Oh, sorry.
Boys... I brought you some snacks...
- Hi.
- ...and something to drink.
- I don’t want you to starve.
- Thanks, that’s nice.
- Sure.
- Thanks, Mommy.
Look... we’ve got a ton of homework.
So, I’ll lock the door, okay?
All right. You don’t mind
if I listen to music
in the living room?
- No, no.
- Not at all.
Well, eat up or the snacks
will get cold
- and they’re perfect.
- Thanks a lot, ma’am.
Welcome.
She’s a very classy lady, right?
- Holy shit, man!
- Have you tried them?
No, but they say at school
they’re the shit.
Open your mouth.
Now? It’s only six o’clock!
Your grandma offered me snacks
and you, some acids.
This is the trip I promised you.
These are the tickets.
How long does the trip last?
About three hours.
You’ll have time
to watch your movie.
All right!
We must wait a while.
Fucking Sapo!
Hello, the text is unread.
Could you upload it again?
IMAGINARY CIRCLE
Shit!
Good morning, sir.
I brought you breakfast.
- Where’s my grandma?
- She left early to do some errands.
- By herself?
- Yes.
Excuse me, sir.
My Blog / Nieves Navarro
About me / Sex: Female
Age: 21 / Occupation: Student
Journalist / Mexico City
I swear my legs
were shaking like jelly.
And although jelly is tacky,
it couldn’t show now.
Quite different
from "Chilangolandia".
Chilang...?
My town.
Why don’t you act for me?
Yes, you must rehearse.
What are you doing?
I’m glad you’re here!
Did you know they change
the window display every Monday?
I won’t miss any.
But look what type of watch.
Yeah, and I’m gonna buy that watch.
I’m gonna be the most famous
actor’s girlfriend, right?
Are you Nieves?
- And are you Fabi...?
- Pig.
Pig, okay.
It’s weird.
I’d never seen you here before.
Frankly, there’s not much to do here.
I know, you read my blog.
Dude, it’s amazing!
I love that you hate
on unpatriotic people!
They ask for it.
Now, even piss-poor peasants
want to be American.
What’s up, dude? Shall we go?
Damn it, man.
Can’t you see I’m busy?
But you said we’d go
on a trip, didn’t you?
Go on a trip?
Do you have “candies”
in your backpack or what?
- Have you tried them?
- Yeah, dude.
With my brother
during vacation last year.
It was fucking awesome!
I’m thinking of selling them here
for twice its value.
No kidding, dude.
If they catch you,
they’ll kick you out.
I think it’s a great business.
You see, pussy!
Shake it off, Yankee!
Well, why don’t you ask
for another chance?
Well, you’ll get another casting.
You already are.
Can’t I have more?
God, Yankee!
I love to spend money with you.
I can be happy with you
even without it.
Being poor is tacky.
Promise me you’ll keep auditioning.
Parents!
They won’t allow you to do
what they couldn’t.
It had never happened
with a girl before.
If you take them all,
it’ll be 80 dollars.
How did it go, dude?
Did you sell them?
Shall we get more?
Dude...
do you like 'Holly'?
- What?
- Nieves, dude.
They call her
Holly Golightly at school.
I know, man!
- But you don’t know why.
- And you do?
Because she’s gone lightly
with everybody.
She’s horny as fuck.
Everybody’s had her.
That’s bullshit, man!
Holly isn’t a slut.
- What’s up, kids!
- Hey!
- How much?
- 112 dollars.
- Caiman, 112!
- I’m coming!
- What is that?
- 112 dollars.
All right!
Anything else?
- Make yourselves at home.
- Thanks.
Have fun.
Damn!
Shall we take them here?
You’re a genius.
What are you reading?
"The Catcher in the Rye".
My grandma gave it to me.
It’s cool.
What is it about?
A boy from New York
that runs away from high school.
And...
What?
What happened next?
Holy shit, dude!
You should get into the school’s
storytelling contest.
No.
I can’t create interesting characters.
So... write about someone you know.
Darling, use the cutlery.
How was your day?
Fine.
The usual.
Have you finished the book?
Try McCarthy,
you might like him!
- Darling?
- I’m sorry, Mom,
but I have to write this
on the computer.
Otherwise, I’ll forget.
Her name was Nieves
and she was perfect.
Listen, I want ten.
Yeah! Today.
In two hours.
All right?
No.
Tomorrow’s better.
I’ll go, okay?
Yeah! About...
fifteen, okay?
Cool!
See you tomorrow.
Wanna hang out?
No, I’ll have supper at home.
Hi, Yankee boy.
What did your mom say?
And what will you do?
Don’t you get it?
Money only abandons the fucked up.
Do I look fucked up?
You aren’t looking for a job.
Well, if we run out of money,
I’ll get more! That’s it!
Listen carefully, Yankee.
It’s the first time I have money,
real money.
If you want to go back to Laredo,
that's your problem.
I’ll stay.
You’re a fucking pig!
Maybe I was doing
something terrible, but...
I felt if Eric got off the train,
Violetta could break down.
What’s up?
Did you forget or what?
Someone found a pill
in the restrooms
and took it to the principal.
Who?
I don’t want any trouble.
Who else knew about my business?
- What do you mean, fucker?
- The principal found out.
What? Holy shit!
They’ll kick you out?
He doesn’t know it was me...
yet.
What, dude?
Who was the fucker who rat on me?
Only Holly Golightly
knows about your business.
Quit it already, okay?
What’s up with her?
Dude, you tell her everything
and you don’t know her well.
I know her better than you,
fucking butt-kisser.
You watch life from the sidelines.
You know what?
I don’t fucking care, dude.
I’m sick of you.
If it wasn’t for me, you’d still be
the fucking outcast
you’ve always been.
I couldn’t care less!
I don’t need you.
So, stay away from me, asshole.
It was me.
What? Why?
I read what you wrote about me.
Did it bother you?
No! Not the fact
that you wrote about me.
It bothered me that you wrote
all those obscenities!
We only kissed!
It’s the story for the contest.
I can write whatever
the fuck I want.
Well, at least
you could have made an effort to,
I don’t know,
change my name, right?
I was going to, obviously.
I was following your advice.
I was writing about somebody I know.
But you don’t know me that well.
- That’s why you made such a fuss?
- Indeed! I got mad,
I stole a pill from you,
took it to the principal,
and told him there was
a dealer at school.
I didn’t mention your name,
but you won’t be
messing around anymore.
You seem open-minded,
but you’re a prude like the others.
Of course I’m not a fucking prude!
Any girl would be grossed out
by a man saying those nasty things!
But you are indeed like the rest.
Why don’t you
keep writing on your blog
and stop making up fairy tales?
Pig!
Come here.
What’s up?
I have cancer.
So?
Are you going to die?
You too?
When?
Never.
Everything will be all right.
Calm down.
Calm down...
Congratulations!
Fuck you, I’m not interested!
I said I’m not interested!
No! Please, no!
Are you okay?
Going down to that basement
was pretty naive.
But I did learn something.
A woman with assets
in the right place...
...has complete power
to rule the world...
No, no, I just wanted to help you.
Where are you going?
What? No!
You can’t go back to the place
that bores you to death.
Please, I need you.
You need me, please.