Eric.
Nobody’s rich in New York.
Not enough, you know?
There’s always something
you can’t have.
It’s hard to admit,
but I couldn’t stop
thinking of Superman.
I ordered the most expensive
dish in the menu.
Just to make up for it.
A hundred thousand dollars.
Fucking Yankee thief!
It felt as if
the universe had conspired
to screw me over.
BASED ON
XAVIER VELASCO'S NOVEL
CHAPTER 3
NEW YORK: TRICK OR TREAT
Darling?
It’s me. Open up.
Open up, darling.
I want to talk with you.
I can’t, I’m busy.
You haven’t had breakfast yet.
Why don’t you come outside
and grab a bite so we can talk?
I’ve a lot of homework.
I understand
that you’re sad, but...
Everything will be fine,
I’ll get well.
I start the treatment today.
I’ll come out later, Mommy,
I promise.
I can’t right now.
I can’t.
What did you do
with my bucks, asshole?
I spent it.
How did you spend
forty fucking thousand dollars?
I don’t want to live
in an apartment,
I live in the best hotel
in the world.
But I do.
I want my bucks.
I just want it.
I don’t want to save.
I trusted you.
Like a typical Yankee,
Eric wasn’t able
to go with the flow,
and foreseeing our poor future,
he thoughtfully rented
a stinky apartment.
Five floors, no lift.
Yeah, for you, asshole.
Even if he was happy,
I felt he had restricted
my freedom.
Who gave him that right,
you know?
New house, new life.
You’re nuts if you think
I’ll live here.
- What?
- It’s awful! Can’t you see?
Call the administrator,
I want my money back.
Why can’t anybody get it?
You’re just like my parents.
A happy ending.
Bye, bye, dreamed life.
Hello, rathole.
At least we’ve got a nice view.
But it is for me.
No need to convince me.
I’m here.
We will freeze during winter.
I’ll keep you warm.
I’ll take care of you.
I’ll protect you.
I hate you.
At first, everything was nice.
Taking showers, kissing,
laughing,
fucking all the time.
You know,
beginnings are always good.
Do you like it?
Long time no see.
- What happened?
- Can I come in?
Sure, come on in.
So?
What will you buy?
Don’t hold back, I’m loaded.
As long as I lose myself,
I don’t fucking care.
Look.
You’ll be really stoned
with these, man, they’re top-notch.
They’re national, you see?
- We’re fucking patriotic.
- Fuck yeah.
Can I take it here?
Sure! The booze is there
if you want some.
Damn it, man.
What are you doing?
I’ll pay for them,
Caiman, no problem.
No, that’s not it.
You already took one,
you can’t take more.
Why not? Who says so?
Because that thing
is really strong,
the trip lasts for hours.
It will last twice as much then.
You’ll be flying all night, man.
- Good.
- You’re really nuts.
Not yet.
Mommy?
Mommy.
Mommy, wake up, Mommy!
- Hello!
- Hi.
I did some shopping.
Hold on.
Hold on, okay?
It’s nice.
When the Yankee started
to do the math,
I could hear the stars falling.
One by one.
I deeply hate
middle-class arithmetic.
I can’t believe how everything
becomes a drag
in a few weeks.
You know me, “Diablo”.
What’s life without passion?
No matter how hard we tried,
we were infinitely different.
Superman was...
I don’t know...
decent, a nice person.
He had all the traits
I lacked.
I felt like yelling at him:
"I want to fuck Lex Luthor!"
I mean it, decent guys
aren’t my style.
Kissing,
the bed and sharing the shower
was a drag.
We were in survival mode.
And I hadn’t come
to New York to survive.
I wanted to live.
And at this pace,
I would end up hating it.
Eric!
I know.
Do you hear me?
Yes. I’m sorry, doctor.
I know you’re having a hard time.
You’re her only close relative.
Sometimes the closeness
and the family support
are better than any treatment.
I’m sorry, doctor.
I just went out for a while,
I thought the maid was with her.
Try not to do it again.
Son of a bitch!
Give me my money, asshole!
Let me go!
Let me go already!
Did you get the bacon?
I forgot.
I don’t know,
whatever you order is fine.
Are you okay?
I’m tired.
I’ll take a shower.
Sorry,
I didn’t want to wake you.
What are you doing here?
Shouldn’t you be at school?
I finished early.
I can read you something
if you want.
Yes, something you wrote?
No. I meant from the novel.
Oh, that’s a shame!
I wanted you to read me something
from your blog.
I guess it must be really funny...
it must be good and fun.
You made me laugh a lot
when you were a kid.
You’re becoming a man.
Don’t worry,
keep doing your thing.
But read me something,
you choose.
Wanna go in?
I’m over here, Yankee.
No, don’t get confused,
I’m much prettier.
Just as Violetta would think
Eric wouldn’t leave her,
Eric would think
that Violetta
could be happy eating bacon
instead of scamming others.
What did I want to prove?
That I was a good thief?
No.
Just that I was capable
of anything.
Only in the States
could you steal an identity.
Mommy.
Let’s see.
If your parents saw
everything you do,
they’d be very proud.
Don’t get used to it.
I’ll stop when you get better.
Go on, Mommy.
Eat up.
It’s toasted.
As we like it.
Yeah, really toasted.
What did they do to you?
Listen, Eric,
I want to live my life
the way I want, I’m sorry.
I was wrong.
I thought I needed you,
but I don’t.
And you don’t need me either.
Eric.
I cried for being such a bitch
and such an ass.
I hate myself
for tearing everything apart.
But I’m also proud of it.
End of the story.
Superman didn’t rescue Violetta.
Mommy.
Wake up.
Are you hungry, darling?
Do you want some chocolate milk?
I'll be back.
Don’t be sad, sweety.
You must be strong
for your grandma.
Your parents are now in heaven
and they’re very happy.
Granny!
Here.
Shoot.
Javier!
What are you doing?
Look Pig, I’m sure there are
many options in your world
of private schools,
big houses
and full fridges.
But in the streets,
there is only one:
Resilience.
Either you have it or not.